effortlessenglishclub.com 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy | Learn to Speak English Powerfully With Effortless English

**Information about our Organization and Web site**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Effortless English LLC . We are based in The USA .

Our principal activity is: English Language Education for Speakers of Other Languages.  We primarily serve adult students.

Our privacy policy covers Effortless English LLC and its Web sites: EffortlessEnglishClub.com, EffortlessEnglish.com

Organization Name: | Effortless English LLC  
---|---  
Address: | 1702 A St, #C  
City, Zip: | Sparks , 89431  
State: | NV  
Country: | USA  
Controller: | Allen Hoge  
Web Sites(s): | EffortlessEnglishClub.com  
  
**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**  
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

**The services and links of our Web site**

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.

Our Web site also includes a link to:

  * Google Adwords

Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors.

**Automatic Collection of Information**

**We may use cookies on our Web site.**

We may automatically log personal data and we may link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.

**Confidentiality / Security**

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:

  * identifiers (such as credit card details, Web site password)

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * unauthorized access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorized modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

You may receive information about the kind of information we have for you by

  * sending an email (members@effortlessenglish.org )

  * mailing us at:  Effortless English LLC, 1702 A Street #C, Sparks, NV 89431

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask us, by:

  * sending an email (members@effortlessenglish.org )
  * mailing us at:  Effortless English LLC, 1702 A Street #C, Sparks, NV 89431

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month. – although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data.

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

**Privacy Support & Removal of Information**

We will remove all of your personal information from our records at your request.

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, or would like your information removed, please contact:

| Contact  
---|---  
Name/designation : | Allen Hoge  
Department : |   
Address : | 1702 A Street #C, Sparks, NV 89431  
Phone Number : |   
Fax Number : |   
Email address : | members@effortlessenglish.org
